Guide to the Texas Monthly Editorial Records
The Wittliff Collections
Texas Monthly Editorial Records
1976-2018
The Wittliff Collections https://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu
Texas Monthly, Inc.; Hall, Michael; Sharpe, Pat; Vine, Katy; Colloff, Pamela; Blakeslee, Nate (1970); Hollandsworth, Skip; Burka, Paul
UPWC.02059
710 Linear Feet
710 boxes
This collection includes editorial files for Texas Monthly issues. The files are arranged chronologically by issue (Date, Year) and are described a tthe box-level. Content of the files per issue vary, but most include fact-check files, author research and notes, inter-office memos, and other materials generated in the composition and publication of feature articles for a particular issue of the magazine.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from Texas Monthly, 1990s to present
Organizational History
Texas Monthly magazine was founded in 1972 by its publisher, Michael R. Levy, a 26 year-old native Dallasite who was "convinced that my state was ready for a really first class magazine that will appeal directly to the sophisticated, cosmopolitan folks that Texans have become." (Texas Monthly, Feb. 1973). Levy brought aboard 27 year-old William Broyles, Jr. as editor. Broyles assembled an editorial staff that was short on journalistic experience but imbued with curiousity, intelligence, irreverence, and literary skills. Many of Texas Monthly's early staffers were friends of Broyles from Rice University, where the intellectual climate helped set the tone for the magazine. As Broyles later wrote, "If any one quality unites these farflung efforts, it is a boundless curiosity. Most of our stories began with one of us saying "I wonder..." (The Best of Texas Monthly: The First Five Years.)
Texas Monthly's first issue was published in February 1973, and it was not an immediate commercial success, selling only about 35,000 copies. But the magazine quickly gained recognition for offering a significant departure from the rest of the state's media. Texas Monthly contained intelligent and entertaining examinations of Texas life ranging from politics, culture, art, sports, personalities, lifestyles, the environment, fashion, crime, business, education, entertainment, and travel. Along the way, the magazine began to define how Texas was emerging as a contemporary urban state while still clinging to its rural mythic past.
From its beginnings, Texas Monthly developed a reputation as a "writer's magazine," and it helped develop new generations of writing talent while also offering a welcome forum for established voices. Texas Monthly hired many young writers as full-time staff members with benefits, creating a community of professional writers centered near the magazine's home base in Austin.
In 1974, after only one year of existence, the editorial staff's efforts were rewarded with a National Magazine Award (the industry equivalent of the Pulitzer Prize) for Specialized Journalism. Since then Texas Monthly has established a solid reputation for editorial excellence, winning eight National Magazine Awards and 38 nominations- a record surpassed by only The New Yorker, The Atlantic Monthly, Harper's and Esquire.
Over the next several decades, Texas Monthly has evolved and changed under new editorships and owners, but it remains the "National Magazine of Texas," chronically life in the Lone Star State, exploring its politics and personalities, barbecue and business, true crime and tacos, honky-tonks and hiking.
Abstract
This collection includes editorial files for Texas Monthly issues. The files are arranged chronologically by issue (Date, Year) and are described at the box-level. Files for a particular issue may be housed across several boxes.
Content of the files per issue vary, but most include fact-check files, author research and notes, inter-office memos, and other materials generated in the composition and publication of feature articles for a particular issue of the magazine.
Following the chronological issue files are a selection of files from a selection of individual writers. And finally, there are other editorial files that contain story ideas, correspondence, and other materials.
Index Terms
Subjects
Periodicals -- Publishing -- Texas; Popular culture
Document Types
Journalism -- Texas
- Issue files, 1976-2017
  - 1976, January (Box 1085)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    2013-024
  - 1979
    - 1979, May (Box 024C/025B)
    - 1979, June (Box 024C/025B)
    - 1979, June (Box 025B)
    - 1979, July (Box 025B)
    - 1979, July (Box 025C/026A/026B)
    - 1979, August (Box 026C/027A)
    - 1979, September (Box 026C/027A)
    - 1979, September (Box 027B)
    - 1979, October (Box 027B)
    - 1979, November (Box 027B)
    - 1979, November (Box 027C/028A)
    - 1979, December (Box 033B/034A)
    - 1979, December (Box 034B)
  - 1980
    - 1980, January (Box 034B)
    - 1980, February (Box 034B)
    - 1980, February (Box 034C/035A)
    - 1980, March (Box 034C/035A)
    - 1980, April (Box 030A)
    - 1980, May (Box 030A)
    - 1980, May (Box 030B)
    - 1980, June (Box 030B)
    - 1980, July (Box 037A)
    - 1980, July (Box 037B/038A)
    - 1980, August (Box 037B/038A)
    - 1980, September (Box 182B/183A)
    - 1980, October (Box 182B/183A)
    - 1980, November (Box 183B)
    - 1980, December (Box 183B)
    - 1980, December (Box 183C/184A)
  - 1981
    - 1981, January (Box 185C/186A)
    - 1981, February (Box 185C/186A)
    - 1981, February (Box 186B)
    - 1981, March (Box 044B/045A)
    - 1981, March (Box 045B)
    - 1981, March (Box 186B)
    - 1981, March (Box 186C/187A)
    - 1981, April (Box 045B)
    - 1981, April (Box 045C/046A)
    - 1981, May (Box 045C/046A)
    - 1981, May (Box 046B)
    - 1981, June (Box 046B)
    - 1981, June (Box 046C/047A)
    - 1981, July (Box 046C/047A)
    - 1981, August (Box 047B)
    - 1981, October (Box 047C/048A)
    - 1981, September (Box 047C/048A)
    - 1981, October (Box 048B)
    - 1981, November (Box 048B)
    - 1981, November (Box 048C/049A)
    - 1981, December (Box 048C/049A)
    - 1981, December (Box 049B)
  - 1982
    - 1982, January (Box 049B)
    - 1982, January (Box 049C/050A)
    - 1982, February (Box 049C/050A)
    - 1982, February (Box 050B)
    - 1982, March (Box 055C/056A)
    - 1982, March (Box 056B)
    - 1982, March (Box 056C/057A)
    - 1982, April (Box 050B)
    - 1982, May (Box 056C/057A)
    - 1982, May (Box 057B)
    - 1982, June (Box 051B/052A)
    - 1982, June (Box 052B)
    - 1982, July (Box 052B)
    - 1982, July (Box 052C/053A)
    - 1982, August (Box 058B/059C)
    - 1982, August (Box 059B)
    - 1982, September (Box 059B)
    - 1982, September (Box 059C/060A)
    - 1982, October (Box 053C/054A)
    - 1982, November (Box 054B/055A)
    - 1982, December (Box 059C/060A)
  - 1983
    - 1983, January (Box 060B)
    - 1983, February (Box 061B/062A)
    - 1983, February (Box 062B)
    - 1983, March (Box 062B)
    - 1983, March (Box 062C/063A)
    - 1983, April (Box 062C/063A)
    - 1983, May (Box 063B/064A)
    - 1983, June (Box 065A)
    - 1983, June (Box 065B/066A)
    - 1983, July (Box 067C/068A)
    - 1983, July (Box 068B)
    - 1983, July (Box 074B/075A)
    - 1983, August (Box 068B)
    - 1983, August (Box 074B/075A)
    - 1983, August (Box 075B)
    - 1983, August (Box 088C/089A)
    - 1983, September (Box 075B)
    - 1983, September (Box 075C/076A)
    - 1983, October (Box 075C/076A)
    - 1983, October (Box 076B)
    - 1983, November (Box 077A)
    - 1983, December (Box 077B)
    - 1983, December (Box 077C/078A)
  - 1984
    - 1984, January (Box 077C/078A)
    - 1984, January (Box 078B)
    - 1984, February (Box 072A)
    - 1984, March (Box 072A)
    - 1984, March (Box 072B/073A)
    - 1984, April (Box 079A)
    - 1984, April (Box 079B)
    - 1984, April (Box 079C/080)
    - 1984, May (Box 079C/080)
    - 1984, May (Box 080B/081A)
    - 1984, June (Box 074A)
    - 1984, July (Box 074A)
    - 1984, July (Box 074B/075A)
    - 1984, August (Box 089B)
    - 1984, September (Box 083B)
    - 1984, September (Box 089B)
    - 1984, October (Box 083C/084A)
    - 1984, October (Box 084B)
    - 1984, October (Box 084C/085A)
    - 1984, November (Box 084C/085A)
    - 1984, November (Box 090C/091A)
    - 1984, November (Box 091C/092A)
    - 1984, December, Box 085B contains a cassette (Box 085B)
    - 1984, December (Box 085C/086A)
  - 1985
    - 1985, January (Box 085C/086A)
    - 1985, January (Box 086B)
    - 1985, February (Box 092C/093A)
    - 1985, February (Box 093B/094A)
    - 1985, March (Box 093B/094A)
    - 1985, March (Box 094B/095A)
    - 1985, April (Box 087B/088A)
    - 1985, April (Box 088B)
    - 1985, May (Box 095B)
    - 1985, May (Box 095C/096A)
    - 1985, June (Box 095C/096A)
    - 1985, June (Box 096C/097A)
    - 1985, July (Box 097B)
    - 1985, July (Box 097C/098A)
    - 1985, August (Box 103C/104A)
    - 1985, August (Box 104B)
    - 1985, August (Box 104C/105A)
    - 1985, September, Box 119B/120A contains Photo (Box 119B/120A)
    - 1985, September (Box 120B)
    - 1985, September (Box 121B)
    - 1985, October (Box 120B)
    - 1985, October (Box 120C/121A)
    - 1985, October (Box 121B)
    - 1985, November (Box 104C/105A)
    - 1985, November (Box 105B)
    - 1985, November (Box 105C/106A)
    - 1985, December (Box 105C/106A)
    - 1985, December (Box 106B)
  - 1986
    - 1986, January (Box 107A)
    - 1986, January (Box 107B)
    - 1986, February (Box 108A)
    - 1986, March (Box 108B)
    - 1986, March (Box 109B/110A)
    - 1986, April (Box 102A)
    - 1986, April (Box 109A)
    - 1986, April (Box 109B/110A)
    - 1986, May (Box 102B/103A)
    - 1986, May (Box 119A)
    - 1986, May, Box 119B/120A contains Photo (Box 119B/120A)
    - 1986, June (Box 118A)
    - 1986, June (Box 118B)
    - 1986, July (Box 109B/110A)
    - 1986, July (Box 110B)
    - 1986, July (Box 118A)
    - 1986, August (Box 110B)
    - 1986, August (Box 110C/111A)
    - 1986, September (Box 112C/113A)
    - 1986, September (Box 113B)
    - 1986, September (Box 113C/114A)
    - 1986, October (Box 120C/121A)
    - 1986, October (Box 121B)
    - 1986, October (Box 121C/122A)
    - 1986, November (Box 113C/114A)
    - 1986, November (Box 114B)
    - 1986, November (Box 115A)
    - 1986, November (Box 115B/116A)
    - 1986, December (Box 115B/116A)
  - 1987
    - 1987, January (Box 116B)
    - 1987, January (Box 116C/117A)
    - 1987, February (Box 123B/124A)
    - 1987, February (Box 124B)
    - 1987, March (Box 124B)
    - 1987, March (Box 124C/125A)
    - 1987, April (Box 329)
    - 1987, April (Box 330)
    - 1987, April (Box 126A)
    - 1987, April (Box 127B/128A)
    - 1987, April (Box 135B)
    - 1987, April (Box 135C/136A)
    - 1987, May (Box 126A)
    - 1987, May (Box 126B)
    - 1987, May (Box 135B)
    - 1987, June (Box 126B)
    - 1987, June (Box 128C/129A)
    - 1987, June (Box 131C/132B)
    - 1987, June (Box 135B)
    - 1987, July (Box 129B)
    - 1987, July (Box 129C/130A)
    - 1987, July (Box 135B)
    - 1987, August (Box 130B/131A)
    - 1987, August (Box 131B)
    - 1987, August (Box 131C/132B)
    - 1987, August (Box 135B)
    - 1987, September (Box 130B/131A)
    - 1987, September (Box 131C/132B)
    - 1987, September (Box 132B)
    - 1987, September (Box 135C/136A)
    - 1987, October (Box 132B)
    - 1987, October (Box 132C/133A)
    - 1987, October (Box 135C/136A)
    - 1987, November (Box 133C/134A)
    - 1987, December (Box 133C/134A)
    - 1987, December (Box 134B/135A)
  - 1988
    - 1988, January (Box 142C/143A)
    - 1988, January (Box 143B)
    - 1988, February (Box 143C/144A)
    - 1988, March (Box 134B/135A)
    - 1988, March (Box 135C/136A)
    - 1988, March (Box 143C/144A)
    - 1988, March (Box 144B)
    - 1988, March (Box 152C/153A)
    - 1988, March (Box 153B)
    - 1988, April (Box 134B/135A)
    - 1988, April (Box 135C/136A)
    - 1988, April (Box 144C/145A)
    - 1988, April (Box 152C/153A)
    - 1988, April (Box 153B)
    - 1988, May (Box 134B/135A)
    - 1988, May (Box 153C/154A)
    - 1988, May (Box 154B)
    - 1988, June (Box 135B)
    - 1988, June (Box 147B/148A)
    - 1988, June (Box 153C/154A)
    - 1988, June (Box 154B)
    - 1988, July (Box 135B)
    - 1988, July (Box 148B)
    - 1988, July (Box 148C/149A)
    - 1988, August (Box 263)
    - 1988, September (Box 263)
    - 1988, September (Box 135C/136A)
    - 1988, October (Box 264)
    - 1988, October (Box 135C/136A)
    - 1988, November (Box 264)
    - 1988, November (Box 148C/149A)
    - 1988, December (Box 685)
      2003-155
    - 1988, December (Box 148C/149A)
    - 1988, December (Box 149B/150A)
    - 1988, December (Box 150B/151A)
  - 1989
    - 1989, January (Box 150B/151A)
    - 1989, January (Box 151B)
    - 1989, February (Box 151C/152A)
    - 1989, February (Box 158C/159A)
    - 1989, February (Box 159B)
    - 1989, March (Box 532)
    - 1989, March (Box 158C/159A)
    - 1989, March (Box 159B)
    - 1989, March (Box 159C/160A)
    - 1989, April (Box 159C/160A)
    - 1989, April (Box 160B)
    - 1989, May (Box 160B)
    - 1989, June (Box 160C/161A)
    - 1989, June (Box 166C/167A)
    - 1989, July (Box 166C/167A)
    - 1989, July (Box 167B)
    - 1989, July (Box 206C/207A)
    - 1989, July (Box 207B/208A)
    - 1989, August (Box 168A)
    - 1989, September (Box 168A)
    - 1989, September (Box 168B/169A)
    - 1989, October (Box 164B)
    - 1989, October (Box 168B/169A)
    - 1989, October (Box 170B/171A)
    - 1989, November (Box 164B)
    - 1989, November (Box 171B/172A)
    - 1989, December (Box 164B)
    - 1989, December (Box 179B/180A)
    - 1989, December (Box 180B)
  - 1990
    - 1990, January (Box 180B)
    - 1990, January (Box 180C/181A)
    - 1990, February (Box 174C/175A)
    - 1990, March (Box 175B/176A)
    - 1990, April (Box 175B/176A)
    - 1990, April (Box 176B)
    - 1990, May (Box 176B)
    - 1990, June (Box 445)
    - 1990, June (Box 176B)
    - 1990, June (Box 176C/177A)
    - 1990, July (Box 176C/177A)
    - 1990, July (Box 177B)
    - 1990, August (Box 177C/178A)
    - 1990, September (Box 265)
    - 1990, September (Box 160C/161A)
    - 1990, October (Box 265)
    - 1990, October (Box 266)
    - 1990, November (Box 177C/178A)
    - 1990, November (Box 178B)
    - 1990, December (Box 160C/161A)
  - 1991
    - 1991 January (Box 178B)
    - 1991, January (Box 178C/179A)
    - 1991, February (Box 267)
    - 1991, March (Box 267)
    - 1991, March (Box 268)
    - 1991, April (Box 268)
    - 1991, April (Box 269)
    - 1991, April (Box 789)
      2006-148
    - 1991, May (Box 269)
    - 1991, June (Box 270)
    - 1991, July (Box 295)
    - 1991, August (Box 294)
    - 1991, August (Box 295)
    - 1991, August (Box 787)
    - 1991, September (Box 294)
    - 1991, September (Box 297)
    - 1991, October (Box 296)
    - 1991, October (Box 297)
    - 1991, November (Box 194C/195A)
    - 1991, November (Box 195B)
    - 1991, December (Box 195B)
    - 1991, December (Box 195C/196A)
  - 1992
    - 1992, January (Box 161B)
    - 1992, January (Box 196B)
    - 1992, January (Box 196C/197A)
    - 1992, February (Box 188B/189A)
    - 1992, February (Box 189B)
    - 1992, February (Box 196B)
    - 1992, March (Box 189B)
    - 1992, March (Box 189C/190A)
    - 1992, April (Box 189C/190A)
    - 1992, April (Box 190C/191A)
    - 1992, April (Box 191B)
    - 1992, May (Box 789)
    - 1992, May (Box 161B)
    - 1992, May (Box 191B)
    - 1992, June (Box 127A)
    - 1992, June (Box 191C/192A)
    - 1992, July (Box 196C/197A)
    - 1992, July (Box 197B)
    - 1992, August (Box 197B)
    - 1992, August (Box 197C/198A)
    - 1992, August (Box 198B)
    - 1992, September (Box 198B)
    - 1992, September (Box 198C/199A)
    - 1992, October (Box 191C/192A)
    - 1992, October (Box 192B)
    - 1992, October (Box 198C/199A)
    - 1992, November (Box 192B)
    - 1992, November (Box 198C/199A)
    - 1992, November (Box 199B)
    - 1992, November (Box 199C/200A)
    - 1992, December (Box 199C/200A)
    - 1992, December (Box 200B)
  - 1993
    - 1993, January (Box 200B)
    - 1993, January (Box 200C/201A)
    - 1993, February (Box 201B)
    - 1993, February (Box 201C/202A)
    - 1993, March (Box 201C/202A)
    - 1993, March (Box 202B)
    - 1993, April (Box 202B)
    - 1993, April (Box 203A)
    - 1993, May (Box 582)
      2002-059
    - 1993, May (Box 597)
    - 1993, May, Box 602 contains photos negatives (Box 602)
    - 1993, May (Box 792)
    - 1993, May (Box 793)
    - 1993, May (Box 794)
    - 1993, May (Box 203A)
    - 1993, May (Box 203B)
    - 1993, June (Box 789)
    - 1993, June (Box 204A)
    - 1993, June (Box 204B/205A)
    - 1993, July (Box 271)
    - 1993, July, Box 595 contains news print (Box 595)
    - 1993, July (Box 204A)
    - 1993, August, Box 272 contains a VHS (Box 272)
    - 1993, August (Box 789)
    - 1993, September (Box 273)
    - 1993, October (Box 274)
    - 1993, October (Box 787)
    - 1993, November (Box 275)
    - 1993, November (Box 276)
    - 1993, December (Box 277)
  - 1994
    - 1994, January (Box 278)
    - 1994, January, Box 279 contains a VHS (Box 279)
    - 1994, February, Box 279 contains a VHS (Box 279)
    - 1994, February (Box 598)
    - 1994, March (Box 280)
    - 1994, April (Box 252)
    - 1994, May, Box 253 contains a VHS (Box 253)
    - 1994, June (Box 281)
    - 1994, July, Box 282 contains a VHS (Box 282)
    - 1994, August (Box 283)
    - 1994, August, Box 284 contains a VHS (Box 284)
    - 1994, September, Box 284 contains a VHS (Box 284)
    - 1994, September (Box 285)
    - 1994, October (Box 286)
    - 1994, October (Box 287)
    - 1994, November (Box 231)
    - 1994, November, Box 288 contains a VHS (Box 288)
    - 1994, November (Box 289)
    - 1994, December (Box 231)
  - 1995
    - 1995, January (Box 244)
    - 1995, January (Box 250)
    - 1995, January (Box 251)
    - 1995, February (Box 250)
    - 1995, February (Box 251)
    - 1995, March (Box 509)
    - 1995, March (Box 533)
    - 1995, April (Box 237)
    - 1995, April (Box 533)
    - 1995, May (Box 236)
    - 1995, May (Box 237)
    - 1995, June (Box 236)
    - 1995, June (Box 237)
    - 1995, June, Box 444 contains a VHS (Box 444)
    - 1995, June (Box 460)
    - 1995, July (Box 443)
    - 1995, July, Box 444 contains a VHS (Box 444)
    - 1995, August (Box 443)
    - 1995, August (Box 460)
    - 1995, September (Box 459)
    - 1995, September (Box 460)
    - 1995, September, Box 483 contains a VHS (Box 483)
    - 1995, September, Box 484 contains a VHS (Box 484)
    - 1995, October, Box 484 contains a VHS (Box 484)
    - 1995, October (Box 485)
    - 1995, November (Box 221)
    - 1995, November (Box 222)
    - 1995, November (Box 223)
    - 1995, December (Box 220)
  - 1996
    - 1996, January (Box 228)
    - 1996, January, Box 230 contains news print (Box 230)
    - 1996, February (Box 228)
    - 1996, February, Box 230 contains news print (Box 230)
    - 1996, February (Box 579)
    - 1996, February (Box 580)
    - 1996, March (Box 579)
    - 1996, March (Box 586)
    - 1996, March (Box 594)
    - 1996, April (Box 557)
    - 1996, April (Box 558)
    - 1996, April (Box 586)
    - 1996, April (Box 594)
    - 1996, May (Box 557)
    - 1996, May (Box 558)
    - 1996, May (Box 606)
      2003-121
    - 1996, May (Box 607)
    - 1996, June (Box 564)
    - 1996, June (Box 565)
    - 1996, June (Box 577)
    - 1996, June (Box 606)
    - 1996, June (Box 607)
    - 1996, July (Box 564)
    - 1996, July (Box 577)
    - 1996, July (Box 578)
    - 1996, August (Box 561)
    - 1996, August (Box 566)
    - 1996, September (Box 567)
    - 1996, September (Box 568)
    - 1996, October (Box 568)
    - 1996, October (Box 583)
    - 1996, October (Box 787)
    - 1996, November (Box 583)
    - 1996, November (Box 584)
    - 1996, December (Box 591)
  - 1997
    - 1997, January (Box 553)
    - 1997, January (Box 554)
    - 1997, January (Box 605)
    - 1997, February (Box 553)
    - 1997, February (Box 554)
    - 1997, February (Box 589)
    - 1997, March (Box 588)
    - 1997, March (Box 589)
    - 1997, April (Box 549)
    - 1997, April (Box 550)
    - 1997, April (Box 588)
    - 1997, April (Box 589)
    - 1997, May (Box 549)
    - 1997, May (Box 550)
    - 1997, May (Box 559)
    - 1997, May (Box 560)
    - 1997, May (Box 561)
    - 1997, May (Box 589)
    - 1997, May (Box 685)
    - 1997, June (Box 550)
    - 1997, June (Box 559)
    - 1997, June (Box 576)
    - 1997, July (Box 555)
    - 1997, July (Box 556)
    - 1997, August (Box 569)
    - 1997, August (Box 570)
    - 1997, September (Box 562)
    - 1997, September (Box 563)
    - 1997, October (Box 563)
    - 1997, October (Box 575)
    - 1997, November (Box 551)
    - 1997, November (Box 571)
    - 1997, November (Box 575)
    - 1997, November (Box 576)
    - 1997, December (Box 571)
    - 1997, December (Box 572)
  - 1998
    - 1998, March, Box 775 contains 2 VHS (Box 775)
    - 1998, March, Box 776 contains 1 VHS (Box 776)
    - 1998, March (Box 777)
    - 1998, April, Box 775 contains 2 VHS (Box 775)
    - 1998, April (Box 778)
    - 1998, May, Box 775 contains 2 VHS (Box 775)
    - 1998, May (Box 778)
    - 1998, June (Box 777)
    - 1998, July (Box 779)
    - 1998, July, Box 780 contains 2 VHS (Box 780)
    - 1998, August (Box 613)
    - 1998, August (Box 779)
    - 1998, August (Box 787)
    - 1998, September (Box 613)
    - 1998, September (Box 614)
    - 1998, October (Box 615)
    - 1998, October (Box 616)
    - 1998, November (Box 617)
    - 1998, November (Box 618)
    - 1998, November (Box 619)
    - 1998, December (Box 618)
    - 1998, December (Box 619)
    - 1998, December (Box 620)
    - 1998, December, Box 786 contains microcassette tapes (Box 786)
  - 1999
    - 1999, January, Box 786 contains microcassette tapes (Box 786)
    - 1999, February (Box 621)
    - 1999, March (Box 621)
    - 1999, March (Box 622)
    - 1999, March (Box 624)
    - 1999, April (Box 623)
    - 1999, April (Box 624)
    - 1999, May (Box 625)
    - 1999, May, Box 626 contains VHS, audio cassettes (Box 626)
    - 1999, June (Box 605)
      2002-072
    - 1999, June (Box 625)
    - 1999, June (Box 627)
    - 1999, July (Box 627)
    - 1999, July (Box 628)
    - 1999, July (Box 629)
    - 1999, August (Box 629)
    - 1999, August (Box 630)
    - 1999, August (Box 632)
    - 1999, September (Box 631)
    - 1999, September (Box 632)
    - 1999, September (Box 672)
    - 1999, October (Box 633)
    - 1999, October (Box 634)
    - 1999, October (Box 873)
      2008-028
    - 1999, November (Box 633)
    - 1999, November (Box 634)
    - 1999, November (Box 635)
    - 1999, December (Box 635)
    - 1999, December (Box 636)
    - 1999, December (Box 637)
  - 2000
    - 2000, January (Box 638)
    - 2000, January (Box 640)
    - 2000, February (Box 639)
    - 2000, February (Box 640)
    - 2000, March (Box 639)
    - 2000, March (Box 640)
    - 2000, March (Box 873)
    - 2000, April (Box 640)
    - 2000, April (Box 641)
    - 2000, April (Box 642)
    - 2000, May (Box 643)
    - 2000, June (Box 646)
    - 2000, June (Box 647)
    - 2000, July (Box 646)
    - 2000, July (Box 648)
    - 2000, August (Box 648)
    - 2000, August (Box 649)
    - 2000, August (Box 675)
    - 2000, October (Box 655)
    - 2000, November (Box 654)
    - 2000, November (Box 655)
    - 2000, November (Box 657)
    - 2000, December (Box 654)
    - 2000, December (Box 656)
    - 2000, December (Box 657)
    - 1995, December (Box 220)
  - 2001
    - 2001, January (Box 660)
    - 2001, January, Box 661 contains a VHS (Box 661)
    - 2001, February (Box 722)
      2005-023
    - 2001, February (Box 663)
    - 2001, March, Box 664 contains a cassette (Box 664)
    - 2001, April (Box 665)
    - 2001, April (Box 669)
    - 2001, May (Box 668)
    - 2001, May (Box 669)
    - 2001, May (Box 670)
    - 2001, June (Box 670)
    - 2001, June (Box 671)